{"problemsArray": [
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(14x + 7)(3x + 1)}/{2x + 1}\\)", "answer": "21x + 7", "explanation": "First, notice that 14x + 7 is 7 times 2x + 1. If we factor out the 7, then we can cancel 2x + 1 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\(7 * (3x + 1).\\)We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 7 into 3x + 1.", "alternatives": ["7 * (3x + 1)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({12x + 6}/{(2x + 1)(3x + 2)}\\)", "answer": "6/(3x + 2)", "explanation": "First, notice that 12x + 6 is 6 times 2x + 1. If we factor out the 6, then we can cancel 2x + 1 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\({6}/{3x + 2}\\).", "alternatives": ["7 * (3x + 1)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({2x + 5}/{(14x + 35)(2x + 3)}\\)", "answer": "1 / (14x + 21)", "explanation": "First, notice that 14x + 35 is 7 times 2x + 5. If we factor out the 7, then we can cancel 2x + 5 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression\\({1}/{7 * (2x + 3)} \\).We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 7 into 2x + 3.", "alternatives": ["1 / (7 * (2x + 3))"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({6x + 4}/{(3x + 2)(2x + 7)}\\)", "answer": "2/(2x + 7)", "explanation": "First, notice that 6x + 4 is 2 times 3x + 2. If we factor out the 2, then we can cancel 3x + 2 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\({2}/{2x + 7}\\).", "alternatives": ["1 / (7 * (2x + 3))"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({3x + 7}/{(15x + 35)(2x + 3)}\\)", "answer": "1 / (10x + 15)", "explanation": "First, notice that 15x + 35 is 5 times 3x + 7. If we factor out the 5, then we can cancel 3x + 7 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression\\({1}/{5 * (2x + 3)} \\).We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 5 into 2x + 3.", "alternatives": ["1 / (5 * (2x + 3))"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({14x + 7}/{(2x + 1)(3x + 7)}\\)", "answer": "7/(3x + 7)", "explanation": "First, notice that 14x + 7 is 7 times 2x + 1. If we factor out the 7, then we can cancel 2x + 1 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\({7}/{3x + 7}\\).", "alternatives": ["1 / (5 * (2x + 3))"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({3x + 1}/{(15x + 5)(3x + 7)}\\)", "answer": "1 / (15x + 35)", "explanation": "First, notice that 15x + 5 is 5 times 3x + 1. If we factor out the 5, then we can cancel 3x + 1 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression\\({1}/{5 * (3x + 7)} \\).We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 5 into 3x + 7.", "alternatives": ["1 / (5 * (3x + 7))"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({2x + 1}/{(14x + 7)(3x + 7)}\\)", "answer": "1 / (21x + 49)", "explanation": "First, notice that 14x + 7 is 7 times 2x + 1. If we factor out the 7, then we can cancel 2x + 1 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression\\({1}/{7 * (3x + 7)} \\).We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 7 into 3x + 7.", "alternatives": ["1 / (7 * (3x + 7))"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(3x + 4)(3x + 7)}/{(21x + 28)}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 7)/7", "explanation": "First, notice that 21x + 28 is 7 times 3x + 4. If we factor out the 7, then we can cancel 3x + 4 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\({3x + 7}/{7}\\).", "alternatives": ["(1/7)(3x + 7)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(18x + 42)(3x + 5)}/{3x + 7}\\)", "answer": "18x + 30", "explanation": "First, notice that 18x + 42 is 6 times 3x + 7. If we factor out the 6, then we can cancel 3x + 7 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\(6 * (3x + 5).\\)We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 6 into 3x + 5.", "alternatives": ["6 * (3x + 5)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(3x + 7)(2x + 1)}/{(6x + 14)}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 1)/2", "explanation": "First, notice that 6x + 14 is 2 times 3x + 7. If we factor out the 2, then we can cancel 3x + 7 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\({2x + 1}/{2}\\).", "alternatives": ["(1/2)(2x + 1)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({3x + 5}/{(18x + 30)(3x + 7)}\\)", "answer": "1 / (18x + 42)", "explanation": "First, notice that 18x + 30 is 6 times 3x + 5. If we factor out the 6, then we can cancel 3x + 5 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression\\({1}/{6 * (3x + 7)} \\).We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 6 into 3x + 7.", "alternatives": ["1 / (6 * (3x + 7))"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(6x + 3)(3x + 1)}/{2x + 1}\\)", "answer": "9x + 3", "explanation": "First, notice that 6x + 3 is 3 times 2x + 1. If we factor out the 3, then we can cancel 2x + 1 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\(3 * (3x + 1).\\)We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 3 into 3x + 1.", "alternatives": ["3 * (3x + 1)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({12x + 6}/{(2x + 1)(3x + 7)}\\)", "answer": "6/(3x + 7)", "explanation": "First, notice that 12x + 6 is 6 times 2x + 1. If we factor out the 6, then we can cancel 2x + 1 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\({6}/{3x + 7}\\).", "alternatives": ["3 * (3x + 1)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(4x + 10)(3x + 7)}/{2x + 5}\\)", "answer": "6x + 14", "explanation": "First, notice that 4x + 10 is 2 times 2x + 5. If we factor out the 2, then we can cancel 2x + 5 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\(2 * (3x + 7).\\)We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 2 into 3x + 7.", "alternatives": ["2 * (3x + 7)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(15x + 25)(2x + 1)}/{3x + 5}\\)", "answer": "10x + 5", "explanation": "First, notice that 15x + 25 is 5 times 3x + 5. If we factor out the 5, then we can cancel 3x + 5 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\(5 * (2x + 1).\\)We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 5 into 2x + 1.", "alternatives": ["5 * (2x + 1)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(2x + 3)(3x + 5)}/{(12x + 18)}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 5)/6", "explanation": "First, notice that 12x + 18 is 6 times 2x + 3. If we factor out the 6, then we can cancel 2x + 3 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\({3x + 5}/{6}\\).", "alternatives": ["(1/6)(3x + 5)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({14x + 49}/{(2x + 7)(3x + 1)}\\)", "answer": "7/(3x + 1)", "explanation": "First, notice that 14x + 49 is 7 times 2x + 7. If we factor out the 7, then we can cancel 2x + 7 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\({7}/{3x + 1}\\).", "alternatives": ["(1/6)(3x + 5)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(3x + 5)(2x + 3)}/{(9x + 15)}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 3)/3", "explanation": "First, notice that 9x + 15 is 3 times 3x + 5. If we factor out the 3, then we can cancel 3x + 5 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\({2x + 3}/{3}\\).", "alternatives": ["(1/3)(2x + 3)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(3x + 5)(3x + 7)}/{(9x + 15)}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 7)/3", "explanation": "First, notice that 9x + 15 is 3 times 3x + 5. If we factor out the 3, then we can cancel 3x + 5 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\({3x + 7}/{3}\\).", "alternatives": ["(1/3)(3x + 7)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(3x + 4)(3x + 7)}/{(12x + 16)}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 7)/4", "explanation": "First, notice that 12x + 16 is 4 times 3x + 4. If we factor out the 4, then we can cancel 3x + 4 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\({3x + 7}/{4}\\).", "alternatives": ["(1/4)(3x + 7)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(14x + 21)(3x + 7)}/{2x + 3}\\)", "answer": "21x + 49", "explanation": "First, notice that 14x + 21 is 7 times 2x + 3. If we factor out the 7, then we can cancel 2x + 3 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\(7 * (3x + 7).\\)We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 7 into 3x + 7.", "alternatives": ["7 * (3x + 7)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({3x + 4}/{(9x + 12)(3x + 1)}\\)", "answer": "1 / (9x + 3)", "explanation": "First, notice that 9x + 12 is 3 times 3x + 4. If we factor out the 3, then we can cancel 3x + 4 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression\\({1}/{3 * (3x + 1)} \\).We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 3 into 3x + 1.", "alternatives": ["1 / (3 * (3x + 1))"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(6x + 9)(3x + 1)}/{2x + 3}\\)", "answer": "9x + 3", "explanation": "First, notice that 6x + 9 is 3 times 2x + 3. If we factor out the 3, then we can cancel 2x + 3 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\(3 * (3x + 1).\\)We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 3 into 3x + 1.", "alternatives": ["3 * (3x + 1)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(3x + 1)(3x + 2)}/{(18x + 6)}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 2)/6", "explanation": "First, notice that 18x + 6 is 6 times 3x + 1. If we factor out the 6, then we can cancel 3x + 1 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\({3x + 2}/{6}\\).", "alternatives": ["(1/6)(3x + 2)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({15x + 35}/{(3x + 7)(2x + 1)}\\)", "answer": "5/(2x + 1)", "explanation": "First, notice that 15x + 35 is 5 times 3x + 7. If we factor out the 5, then we can cancel 3x + 7 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\({5}/{2x + 1}\\).", "alternatives": ["(1/6)(3x + 2)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(12x + 28)(3x + 1)}/{3x + 7}\\)", "answer": "12x + 4", "explanation": "First, notice that 12x + 28 is 4 times 3x + 7. If we factor out the 4, then we can cancel 3x + 7 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\(4 * (3x + 1).\\)We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 4 into 3x + 1.", "alternatives": ["4 * (3x + 1)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({2x + 5}/{(12x + 30)(3x + 7)}\\)", "answer": "1 / (18x + 42)", "explanation": "First, notice that 12x + 30 is 6 times 2x + 5. If we factor out the 6, then we can cancel 2x + 5 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression\\({1}/{6 * (3x + 7)} \\).We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 6 into 3x + 7.", "alternatives": ["1 / (6 * (3x + 7))"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({3x + 5}/{(18x + 30)(2x + 1)}\\)", "answer": "1 / (12x + 6)", "explanation": "First, notice that 18x + 30 is 6 times 3x + 5. If we factor out the 6, then we can cancel 3x + 5 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression\\({1}/{6 * (2x + 1)} \\).We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 6 into 2x + 1.", "alternatives": ["1 / (6 * (2x + 1))"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({14x + 35}/{(2x + 5)(3x + 4)}\\)", "answer": "7/(3x + 4)", "explanation": "First, notice that 14x + 35 is 7 times 2x + 5. If we factor out the 7, then we can cancel 2x + 5 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\({7}/{3x + 4}\\).", "alternatives": ["1 / (6 * (2x + 1))"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({3x + 7}/{(12x + 28)(3x + 5)}\\)", "answer": "1 / (12x + 20)", "explanation": "First, notice that 12x + 28 is 4 times 3x + 7. If we factor out the 4, then we can cancel 3x + 7 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression\\({1}/{4 * (3x + 5)} \\).We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 4 into 3x + 5.", "alternatives": ["1 / (4 * (3x + 5))"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(3x + 5)(2x + 3)}/{(12x + 20)}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 3)/4", "explanation": "First, notice that 12x + 20 is 4 times 3x + 5. If we factor out the 4, then we can cancel 3x + 5 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\({2x + 3}/{4}\\).", "alternatives": ["(1/4)(2x + 3)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(2x + 7)(2x + 1)}/{(8x + 28)}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 1)/4", "explanation": "First, notice that 8x + 28 is 4 times 2x + 7. If we factor out the 4, then we can cancel 2x + 7 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\({2x + 1}/{4}\\).", "alternatives": ["(1/4)(2x + 1)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({14x + 7}/{(2x + 1)(3x + 7)}\\)", "answer": "7/(3x + 7)", "explanation": "First, notice that 14x + 7 is 7 times 2x + 1. If we factor out the 7, then we can cancel 2x + 1 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\({7}/{3x + 7}\\).", "alternatives": ["(1/4)(2x + 1)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({10x + 25}/{(2x + 5)(3x + 2)}\\)", "answer": "5/(3x + 2)", "explanation": "First, notice that 10x + 25 is 5 times 2x + 5. If we factor out the 5, then we can cancel 2x + 5 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\({5}/{3x + 2}\\).", "alternatives": ["(1/4)(2x + 1)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(2x + 3)(2x + 7)}/{(6x + 9)}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 7)/3", "explanation": "First, notice that 6x + 9 is 3 times 2x + 3. If we factor out the 3, then we can cancel 2x + 3 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\({2x + 7}/{3}\\).", "alternatives": ["(1/3)(2x + 7)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(18x + 12)(2x + 3)}/{3x + 2}\\)", "answer": "12x + 18", "explanation": "First, notice that 18x + 12 is 6 times 3x + 2. If we factor out the 6, then we can cancel 3x + 2 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\(6 * (2x + 3).\\)We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 6 into 2x + 3.", "alternatives": ["6 * (2x + 3)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(3x + 5)(3x + 4)}/{(9x + 15)}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 4)/3", "explanation": "First, notice that 9x + 15 is 3 times 3x + 5. If we factor out the 3, then we can cancel 3x + 5 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\({3x + 4}/{3}\\).", "alternatives": ["(1/3)(3x + 4)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(4x + 10)(3x + 2)}/{2x + 5}\\)", "answer": "6x + 4", "explanation": "First, notice that 4x + 10 is 2 times 2x + 5. If we factor out the 2, then we can cancel 2x + 5 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\(2 * (3x + 2).\\)We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 2 into 3x + 2.", "alternatives": ["2 * (3x + 2)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(4x + 2)(2x + 5)}/{2x + 1}\\)", "answer": "4x + 10", "explanation": "First, notice that 4x + 2 is 2 times 2x + 1. If we factor out the 2, then we can cancel 2x + 1 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\(2 * (2x + 5).\\)We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 2 into 2x + 5.", "alternatives": ["2 * (2x + 5)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({12x + 20}/{(3x + 5)(2x + 1)}\\)", "answer": "4/(2x + 1)", "explanation": "First, notice that 12x + 20 is 4 times 3x + 5. If we factor out the 4, then we can cancel 3x + 5 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\({4}/{2x + 1}\\).", "alternatives": ["2 * (2x + 5)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({3x + 5}/{(18x + 30)(2x + 5)}\\)", "answer": "1 / (12x + 30)", "explanation": "First, notice that 18x + 30 is 6 times 3x + 5. If we factor out the 6, then we can cancel 3x + 5 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression\\({1}/{6 * (2x + 5)} \\).We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 6 into 2x + 5.", "alternatives": ["1 / (6 * (2x + 5))"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({21x + 28}/{(3x + 4)(2x + 1)}\\)", "answer": "7/(2x + 1)", "explanation": "First, notice that 21x + 28 is 7 times 3x + 4. If we factor out the 7, then we can cancel 3x + 4 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\({7}/{2x + 1}\\).", "alternatives": ["1 / (6 * (2x + 5))"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(6x + 4)(3x + 5)}/{3x + 2}\\)", "answer": "6x + 10", "explanation": "First, notice that 6x + 4 is 2 times 3x + 2. If we factor out the 2, then we can cancel 3x + 2 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\(2 * (3x + 5).\\)We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 2 into 3x + 5.", "alternatives": ["2 * (3x + 5)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(15x + 5)(3x + 2)}/{3x + 1}\\)", "answer": "15x + 10", "explanation": "First, notice that 15x + 5 is 5 times 3x + 1. If we factor out the 5, then we can cancel 3x + 1 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\(5 * (3x + 2).\\)We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 5 into 3x + 2.", "alternatives": ["5 * (3x + 2)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(3x + 4)(3x + 2)}/{(15x + 20)}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 2)/5", "explanation": "First, notice that 15x + 20 is 5 times 3x + 4. If we factor out the 5, then we can cancel 3x + 4 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\({3x + 2}/{5}\\).", "alternatives": ["(1/5)(3x + 2)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(3x + 7)(3x + 5)}/{(18x + 42)}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 5)/6", "explanation": "First, notice that 18x + 42 is 6 times 3x + 7. If we factor out the 6, then we can cancel 3x + 7 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\({3x + 5}/{6}\\).", "alternatives": ["(1/6)(3x + 5)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({3x + 4}/{(12x + 16)(2x + 1)}\\)", "answer": "1 / (8x + 4)", "explanation": "First, notice that 12x + 16 is 4 times 3x + 4. If we factor out the 4, then we can cancel 3x + 4 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression\\({1}/{4 * (2x + 1)} \\).We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 4 into 2x + 1.", "alternatives": ["1 / (4 * (2x + 1))"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({2x + 7}/{(14x + 49)(3x + 7)}\\)", "answer": "1 / (21x + 49)", "explanation": "First, notice that 14x + 49 is 7 times 2x + 7. If we factor out the 7, then we can cancel 2x + 7 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression\\({1}/{7 * (3x + 7)} \\).We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 7 into 3x + 7.", "alternatives": ["1 / (7 * (3x + 7))"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({9x + 15}/{(3x + 5)(2x + 3)}\\)", "answer": "3/(2x + 3)", "explanation": "First, notice that 9x + 15 is 3 times 3x + 5. If we factor out the 3, then we can cancel 3x + 5 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\({3}/{2x + 3}\\).", "alternatives": ["1 / (7 * (3x + 7))"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({9x + 3}/{(3x + 1)(3x + 2)}\\)", "answer": "3/(3x + 2)", "explanation": "First, notice that 9x + 3 is 3 times 3x + 1. If we factor out the 3, then we can cancel 3x + 1 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\({3}/{3x + 2}\\).", "alternatives": ["1 / (7 * (3x + 7))"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(2x + 1)(3x + 1)}/{(4x + 2)}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 1)/2", "explanation": "First, notice that 4x + 2 is 2 times 2x + 1. If we factor out the 2, then we can cancel 2x + 1 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\({3x + 1}/{2}\\).", "alternatives": ["(1/2)(3x + 1)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({3x + 2}/{(6x + 4)(3x + 1)}\\)", "answer": "1 / (6x + 2)", "explanation": "First, notice that 6x + 4 is 2 times 3x + 2. If we factor out the 2, then we can cancel 3x + 2 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression\\({1}/{2 * (3x + 1)} \\).We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 2 into 3x + 1.", "alternatives": ["1 / (2 * (3x + 1))"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({2x + 3}/{(4x + 6)(3x + 2)}\\)", "answer": "1 / (6x + 4)", "explanation": "First, notice that 4x + 6 is 2 times 2x + 3. If we factor out the 2, then we can cancel 2x + 3 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression\\({1}/{2 * (3x + 2)} \\).We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 2 into 3x + 2.", "alternatives": ["1 / (2 * (3x + 2))"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({15x + 20}/{(3x + 4)(2x + 7)}\\)", "answer": "5/(2x + 7)", "explanation": "First, notice that 15x + 20 is 5 times 3x + 4. If we factor out the 5, then we can cancel 3x + 4 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\({5}/{2x + 7}\\).", "alternatives": ["1 / (2 * (3x + 2))"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({9x + 21}/{(3x + 7)(3x + 4)}\\)", "answer": "3/(3x + 4)", "explanation": "First, notice that 9x + 21 is 3 times 3x + 7. If we factor out the 3, then we can cancel 3x + 7 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\({3}/{3x + 4}\\).", "alternatives": ["1 / (2 * (3x + 2))"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(3x + 5)(3x + 1)}/{(6x + 10)}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 1)/2", "explanation": "First, notice that 6x + 10 is 2 times 3x + 5. If we factor out the 2, then we can cancel 3x + 5 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\({3x + 1}/{2}\\).", "alternatives": ["(1/2)(3x + 1)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({3x + 4}/{(6x + 8)(3x + 7)}\\)", "answer": "1 / (6x + 14)", "explanation": "First, notice that 6x + 8 is 2 times 3x + 4. If we factor out the 2, then we can cancel 3x + 4 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression\\({1}/{2 * (3x + 7)} \\).We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 2 into 3x + 7.", "alternatives": ["1 / (2 * (3x + 7))"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({3x + 4}/{(15x + 20)(2x + 1)}\\)", "answer": "1 / (10x + 5)", "explanation": "First, notice that 15x + 20 is 5 times 3x + 4. If we factor out the 5, then we can cancel 3x + 4 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression\\({1}/{5 * (2x + 1)} \\).We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 5 into 2x + 1.", "alternatives": ["1 / (5 * (2x + 1))"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({3x + 2}/{(9x + 6)(2x + 5)}\\)", "answer": "1 / (6x + 15)", "explanation": "First, notice that 9x + 6 is 3 times 3x + 2. If we factor out the 3, then we can cancel 3x + 2 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression\\({1}/{3 * (2x + 5)} \\).We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 3 into 2x + 5.", "alternatives": ["1 / (3 * (2x + 5))"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(12x + 16)(3x + 2)}/{3x + 4}\\)", "answer": "12x + 8", "explanation": "First, notice that 12x + 16 is 4 times 3x + 4. If we factor out the 4, then we can cancel 3x + 4 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\(4 * (3x + 2).\\)We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 4 into 3x + 2.", "alternatives": ["4 * (3x + 2)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(15x + 25)(3x + 1)}/{3x + 5}\\)", "answer": "15x + 5", "explanation": "First, notice that 15x + 25 is 5 times 3x + 5. If we factor out the 5, then we can cancel 3x + 5 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\(5 * (3x + 1).\\)We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 5 into 3x + 1.", "alternatives": ["5 * (3x + 1)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(2x + 3)(3x + 4)}/{(10x + 15)}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 4)/5", "explanation": "First, notice that 10x + 15 is 5 times 2x + 3. If we factor out the 5, then we can cancel 2x + 3 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\({3x + 4}/{5}\\).", "alternatives": ["(1/5)(3x + 4)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({15x + 5}/{(3x + 1)(2x + 7)}\\)", "answer": "5/(2x + 7)", "explanation": "First, notice that 15x + 5 is 5 times 3x + 1. If we factor out the 5, then we can cancel 3x + 1 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\({5}/{2x + 7}\\).", "alternatives": ["(1/5)(3x + 4)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(2x + 1)(3x + 7)}/{(4x + 2)}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 7)/2", "explanation": "First, notice that 4x + 2 is 2 times 2x + 1. If we factor out the 2, then we can cancel 2x + 1 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\({3x + 7}/{2}\\).", "alternatives": ["(1/2)(3x + 7)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({2x + 7}/{(10x + 35)(3x + 7)}\\)", "answer": "1 / (15x + 35)", "explanation": "First, notice that 10x + 35 is 5 times 2x + 7. If we factor out the 5, then we can cancel 2x + 7 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression\\({1}/{5 * (3x + 7)} \\).We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 5 into 3x + 7.", "alternatives": ["1 / (5 * (3x + 7))"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({6x + 2}/{(3x + 1)(2x + 5)}\\)", "answer": "2/(2x + 5)", "explanation": "First, notice that 6x + 2 is 2 times 3x + 1. If we factor out the 2, then we can cancel 3x + 1 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\({2}/{2x + 5}\\).", "alternatives": ["1 / (5 * (3x + 7))"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(3x + 1)(2x + 3)}/{(21x + 7)}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 3)/7", "explanation": "First, notice that 21x + 7 is 7 times 3x + 1. If we factor out the 7, then we can cancel 3x + 1 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\({2x + 3}/{7}\\).", "alternatives": ["(1/7)(2x + 3)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(12x + 8)(2x + 7)}/{3x + 2}\\)", "answer": "8x + 28", "explanation": "First, notice that 12x + 8 is 4 times 3x + 2. If we factor out the 4, then we can cancel 3x + 2 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\(4 * (2x + 7).\\)We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 4 into 2x + 7.", "alternatives": ["4 * (2x + 7)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({2x + 7}/{(10x + 35)(2x + 3)}\\)", "answer": "1 / (10x + 15)", "explanation": "First, notice that 10x + 35 is 5 times 2x + 7. If we factor out the 5, then we can cancel 2x + 7 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression\\({1}/{5 * (2x + 3)} \\).We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 5 into 2x + 3.", "alternatives": ["1 / (5 * (2x + 3))"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(4x + 6)(3x + 2)}/{2x + 3}\\)", "answer": "6x + 4", "explanation": "First, notice that 4x + 6 is 2 times 2x + 3. If we factor out the 2, then we can cancel 2x + 3 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\(2 * (3x + 2).\\)We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 2 into 3x + 2.", "alternatives": ["2 * (3x + 2)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({18x + 6}/{(3x + 1)(3x + 7)}\\)", "answer": "6/(3x + 7)", "explanation": "First, notice that 18x + 6 is 6 times 3x + 1. If we factor out the 6, then we can cancel 3x + 1 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\({6}/{3x + 7}\\).", "alternatives": ["2 * (3x + 2)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(2x + 3)(3x + 4)}/{(10x + 15)}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 4)/5", "explanation": "First, notice that 10x + 15 is 5 times 2x + 3. If we factor out the 5, then we can cancel 2x + 3 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\({3x + 4}/{5}\\).", "alternatives": ["(1/5)(3x + 4)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(15x + 10)(3x + 7)}/{3x + 2}\\)", "answer": "15x + 35", "explanation": "First, notice that 15x + 10 is 5 times 3x + 2. If we factor out the 5, then we can cancel 3x + 2 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\(5 * (3x + 7).\\)We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 5 into 3x + 7.", "alternatives": ["5 * (3x + 7)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(6x + 2)(2x + 1)}/{3x + 1}\\)", "answer": "4x + 2", "explanation": "First, notice that 6x + 2 is 2 times 3x + 1. If we factor out the 2, then we can cancel 3x + 1 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\(2 * (2x + 1).\\)We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 2 into 2x + 1.", "alternatives": ["2 * (2x + 1)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(21x + 35)(2x + 1)}/{3x + 5}\\)", "answer": "14x + 7", "explanation": "First, notice that 21x + 35 is 7 times 3x + 5. If we factor out the 7, then we can cancel 3x + 5 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\(7 * (2x + 1).\\)We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 7 into 2x + 1.", "alternatives": ["7 * (2x + 1)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(3x + 1)(2x + 3)}/{(21x + 7)}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 3)/7", "explanation": "First, notice that 21x + 7 is 7 times 3x + 1. If we factor out the 7, then we can cancel 3x + 1 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\({2x + 3}/{7}\\).", "alternatives": ["(1/7)(2x + 3)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({6x + 21}/{(2x + 7)(2x + 5)}\\)", "answer": "3/(2x + 5)", "explanation": "First, notice that 6x + 21 is 3 times 2x + 7. If we factor out the 3, then we can cancel 2x + 7 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\({3}/{2x + 5}\\).", "alternatives": ["(1/7)(2x + 3)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(12x + 20)(3x + 7)}/{3x + 5}\\)", "answer": "12x + 28", "explanation": "First, notice that 12x + 20 is 4 times 3x + 5. If we factor out the 4, then we can cancel 3x + 5 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\(4 * (3x + 7).\\)We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 4 into 3x + 7.", "alternatives": ["4 * (3x + 7)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({6x + 8}/{(3x + 4)(3x + 5)}\\)", "answer": "2/(3x + 5)", "explanation": "First, notice that 6x + 8 is 2 times 3x + 4. If we factor out the 2, then we can cancel 3x + 4 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\({2}/{3x + 5}\\).", "alternatives": ["4 * (3x + 7)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({15x + 35}/{(3x + 7)(2x + 5)}\\)", "answer": "5/(2x + 5)", "explanation": "First, notice that 15x + 35 is 5 times 3x + 7. If we factor out the 5, then we can cancel 3x + 7 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\({5}/{2x + 5}\\).", "alternatives": ["4 * (3x + 7)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(2x + 5)(2x + 1)}/{(4x + 10)}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 1)/2", "explanation": "First, notice that 4x + 10 is 2 times 2x + 5. If we factor out the 2, then we can cancel 2x + 5 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\({2x + 1}/{2}\\).", "alternatives": ["(1/2)(2x + 1)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({14x + 49}/{(2x + 7)(2x + 3)}\\)", "answer": "7/(2x + 3)", "explanation": "First, notice that 14x + 49 is 7 times 2x + 7. If we factor out the 7, then we can cancel 2x + 7 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\({7}/{2x + 3}\\).", "alternatives": ["(1/2)(2x + 1)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(18x + 24)(2x + 3)}/{3x + 4}\\)", "answer": "12x + 18", "explanation": "First, notice that 18x + 24 is 6 times 3x + 4. If we factor out the 6, then we can cancel 3x + 4 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\(6 * (2x + 3).\\)We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 6 into 2x + 3.", "alternatives": ["6 * (2x + 3)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(18x + 30)(2x + 7)}/{3x + 5}\\)", "answer": "12x + 42", "explanation": "First, notice that 18x + 30 is 6 times 3x + 5. If we factor out the 6, then we can cancel 3x + 5 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\(6 * (2x + 7).\\)We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 6 into 2x + 7.", "alternatives": ["6 * (2x + 7)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(18x + 42)(2x + 3)}/{3x + 7}\\)", "answer": "12x + 18", "explanation": "First, notice that 18x + 42 is 6 times 3x + 7. If we factor out the 6, then we can cancel 3x + 7 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\(6 * (2x + 3).\\)We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 6 into 2x + 3.", "alternatives": ["6 * (2x + 3)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(8x + 12)(3x + 4)}/{2x + 3}\\)", "answer": "12x + 16", "explanation": "First, notice that 8x + 12 is 4 times 2x + 3. If we factor out the 4, then we can cancel 2x + 3 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\(4 * (3x + 4).\\)We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 4 into 3x + 4.", "alternatives": ["4 * (3x + 4)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({2x + 1}/{(6x + 3)(3x + 2)}\\)", "answer": "1 / (9x + 6)", "explanation": "First, notice that 6x + 3 is 3 times 2x + 1. If we factor out the 3, then we can cancel 2x + 1 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression\\({1}/{3 * (3x + 2)} \\).We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 3 into 3x + 2.", "alternatives": ["1 / (3 * (3x + 2))"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({9x + 21}/{(3x + 7)(3x + 5)}\\)", "answer": "3/(3x + 5)", "explanation": "First, notice that 9x + 21 is 3 times 3x + 7. If we factor out the 3, then we can cancel 3x + 7 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\({3}/{3x + 5}\\).", "alternatives": ["1 / (3 * (3x + 2))"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({6x + 4}/{(3x + 2)(2x + 5)}\\)", "answer": "2/(2x + 5)", "explanation": "First, notice that 6x + 4 is 2 times 3x + 2. If we factor out the 2, then we can cancel 3x + 2 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\({2}/{2x + 5}\\).", "alternatives": ["1 / (3 * (3x + 2))"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(2x + 7)(2x + 1)}/{(12x + 42)}\\)", "answer": "(2x + 1)/6", "explanation": "First, notice that 12x + 42 is 6 times 2x + 7. If we factor out the 6, then we can cancel 2x + 7 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\({2x + 1}/{6}\\).", "alternatives": ["(1/6)(2x + 1)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({4x + 10}/{(2x + 5)(3x + 1)}\\)", "answer": "2/(3x + 1)", "explanation": "First, notice that 4x + 10 is 2 times 2x + 5. If we factor out the 2, then we can cancel 2x + 5 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\({2}/{3x + 1}\\).", "alternatives": ["(1/6)(2x + 1)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(3x + 5)(3x + 4)}/{(21x + 35)}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 4)/7", "explanation": "First, notice that 21x + 35 is 7 times 3x + 5. If we factor out the 7, then we can cancel 3x + 5 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\({3x + 4}/{7}\\).", "alternatives": ["(1/7)(3x + 4)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({3x + 5}/{(12x + 20)(2x + 7)}\\)", "answer": "1 / (8x + 28)", "explanation": "First, notice that 12x + 20 is 4 times 3x + 5. If we factor out the 4, then we can cancel 3x + 5 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression\\({1}/{4 * (2x + 7)} \\).We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 4 into 2x + 7.", "alternatives": ["1 / (4 * (2x + 7))"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(18x + 6)(2x + 3)}/{3x + 1}\\)", "answer": "12x + 18", "explanation": "First, notice that 18x + 6 is 6 times 3x + 1. If we factor out the 6, then we can cancel 3x + 1 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\(6 * (2x + 3).\\)We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 6 into 2x + 3.", "alternatives": ["6 * (2x + 3)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({3x + 7}/{(15x + 35)(2x + 5)}\\)", "answer": "1 / (10x + 25)", "explanation": "First, notice that 15x + 35 is 5 times 3x + 7. If we factor out the 5, then we can cancel 3x + 7 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression\\({1}/{5 * (2x + 5)} \\).We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 5 into 2x + 5.", "alternatives": ["1 / (5 * (2x + 5))"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({2x + 3}/{(10x + 15)(3x + 4)}\\)", "answer": "1 / (15x + 20)", "explanation": "First, notice that 10x + 15 is 5 times 2x + 3. If we factor out the 5, then we can cancel 2x + 3 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression\\({1}/{5 * (3x + 4)} \\).We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 5 into 3x + 4.", "alternatives": ["1 / (5 * (3x + 4))"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({3x + 1}/{(15x + 5)(2x + 7)}\\)", "answer": "1 / (10x + 35)", "explanation": "First, notice that 15x + 5 is 5 times 3x + 1. If we factor out the 5, then we can cancel 3x + 1 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression\\({1}/{5 * (2x + 7)} \\).We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 5 into 2x + 7.", "alternatives": ["1 / (5 * (2x + 7))"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(6x + 14)(2x + 1)}/{3x + 7}\\)", "answer": "4x + 2", "explanation": "First, notice that 6x + 14 is 2 times 3x + 7. If we factor out the 2, then we can cancel 3x + 7 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\(2 * (2x + 1).\\)We can either leave this as the final answer or simplify it further by distributing the 2 into 2x + 1.", "alternatives": ["2 * (2x + 1)"]},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Simplify:\n\\({(3x + 5)(3x + 2)}/{(21x + 35)}\\)", "answer": "(3x + 2)/7", "explanation": "First, notice that 21x + 35 is 7 times 3x + 5. If we factor out the 7, then we can cancel 3x + 5 from both the numerator and the denominator.\nThis leaves the rational expression \\({3x + 2}/{7}\\).", "alternatives": ["(1/7)(3x + 2)"]}
]}